#### Contact

7193778765 (Mobile) jkrus67@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/krusejohna (LinkedIn) krusejohn.github.io/Portfolio/ (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

JavaScript jQuery Bootstrap

# John Kruse

Student at University of Denver - University College Colorado Springs, Colorado

## Summary

Full-stack web developer with extensive background as a magnetic resonance imaging technologist. Not long ago, I retired from the healthcare industry after 25 rewarding years. Wanting to remain in a technical field, and knowing I have a lot to contribute, I began exploring computer programming as this has always piqued my interest. After extensive research, I decided to enroll in a full-stack web development program offered at Denver University.

## Experience

University of Denver - University College Student November 2018 - Present

TruGreen Senior Specialist 2016 - Present

Colorado Springs, Colorado Area

- Application technician providing lawn, tree, and shrub fertilization.
- Weed, insect, and disease identification and control.
- Proper chemical handling and safety.
- Qualified Supervisor accreditation from State of Colorado Department of Agriculture.
- Professional, reliable customer service.

H&R Block
H&R Block Tax Associate
2015 - 2016 (2 years)
Colorado Springs, Colorado Area

- Tax Associate preparing individual tax returns to new and returning clients.
- Interviewed clients, insuring maximum refund or lowest tax due according to client's tax history.
- Data entry into BlockWorks tax software.
- Advised clients of how to minimize yearly tax liability.

# Colorado Springs Health Partners, a DaVita Medical Group Lead MRI Technologist

2012 - 2014 (3 years)

Colorado Springs, Colorado Area

- MRI Technologist operating a Toshiba MRI scanner in a clinical setting.
- Responsibilities included overseeing and implementing ACR/QA/QC guidelines.
- MRI scanning protocol development and revision.

Alliance Medical Diagnostic Imaging Ltd MRI Technologist 2010 - 2012 (3 years)

Greater Denver Area

- MRI Technologist servicing two facilities in the Denver area utilizing a GE MRI system in a mobile environment.
- Completed competency reports of staff MRI technologists for the regional manager.

Western Mobile Services
MRI Technologist
2006 - 2010 (5 years)

Colorado and New Mexico

- Mobile MRI Technologist servicing rural hospitals in Colorado and New Mexico.
- Operated Siemens MRI system.

### Education

University of Denver

Full-Stack Web Development · (2018 - 2019)

Rice Memorial Hospital School of Radiologic Technology
Associate of Science - AS, Radiologic Technology/Science - Radiographer